So my heartfelt thanks to all of you. We are doing a
program with Jeevika Didi
where we are running the awareness campaign of Bhim in the border areas.
This is
a first from our idea in which they have decided
that from 2000 every citizen of India should be
insured and in this,
we have started this Mahim in Bihar,
ICC Lombard and
Milk. Here we go to the villages and give
them Milk
and Milk. We try to give this message through the medium that the
circumstances are changing day by day.
Talk about business, health
and those other people who did not have it,
show the difference between the two. In
our country, the
annual premium amount that we have to
pay for wife's insurance is much more than what is spent on tea and water,
which does not have any good effect on the body.
But insurance is such a thing that it takes
less time when there is a lot of need, when
your resources are needed to fulfill other needs,
that time is insurance.